[Music]
the same
destination you're W to together as
one in this place there's only one
vision and that's to be the number
one the right comination
comination there's no
compromise doing the very best will be
our mission
something that we need to
realize is something very special in
our we
are
of we are the
[Music]
people you never Reon to believe
we are number
[Music]
one right comination
comination and finding there's no
compromise doing the very best will be
our mission
something that we need to
realize it's something very special in
our we
are we are the
people we never had a reason to believe
we are number one we are number
one we